Oshi Culture
This program focuses on anime, games, manga and other
This program focuses on the staff rolls of various guess contents
This is the show where we listen to the ego-boosting of the people who create the content!
This time
We are going to feature the live performance of Ebichu!
A special feature on the live performance of Ebichu!
In the guess culture, we are going to show you the cute side of idols and the unstable side of idols that makes you nervous.
They talk about the cute side of idols and the unstable side that makes the viewers nervous.
But the girls really come into their own at their live performances in front of
live performance in front of more than 10,000 people.
In the past, they called their live performances "King of Arts and Crafts
They called themselves the "King of the Arts and Sciences".
They used to sell their lackluster dancing and unstable singing ability in a self-deprecating way, but now, 15 years after their formation, they have become the most popular idol group in Japan.
But now, 15 years after their formation, they are one of the best performers in the idol world.
Now, 15 years after its formation, the group has grown to become one of the most admired groups in the idol world for its outstanding performances and wide range of songs.
This time, we will listen to the self-praise of the craftsmen in the staff roll who create Ebitu Live and dig deeper into its appeal.
We will delve deeper into the appeal of the group.
Ebichu Live
A quick staff roll search
The first titles that caught my attention were
FOH engineer and monitor engineer
When I visited the site where Ebitu Live is being held
FOH engineer and monitor engineer, Mr. Kobayashi and Mr. Shoji.
I heard that each of them is in the field of sound engineering.
of a live performance of a song
They are in charge of the sound adjustment of the live sound that the audience is listening to.
They are in charge of adjusting the sound that the audience is listening to.
the size of the venue, the orchestra, the instruments, etc.
I try to bring the sound to the best condition for the space.
I am in charge of adjusting the sound to the best condition for the venue, orchestra, instruments, etc.
I adjust the volume and the mix of the sound to suit the audience's ears.
I adjust the volume and the mix of the instruments in their ears.
The earphones that the members wear in their ears are called ear monitors.
The monitor engineer's job is to deliver the sound to these earphones.
Each member has his or her own preference, and I adjust the volume of my voice and the volume of the other members' voices.
The balance of the volume of the other members' voices
The engineer balances the volume of his own voice against the volume of the other members' voices, the highs and lows of the other sound sources, and so on.
I adjust the sound for each member to make it easier for them to sing.
Two of them, who listen to the members' voices closer than anyone else, told us about the members' personalities.
They told us about the members' personalities.
We all work hard, but the way we work is a little different.
But the way they work hard is a little bit different.
Maya Maya's low mitts come out really well.
It's probably the most sexy voice.
Hey, I got all wet with tears.
Mouma has the most sex appeal of anyone.
When he decides to do something right...
I think it's the best.
If you're into it...
Mr. Kokuho...
Can I say that?
Yes, sir.
I'm working on my solo.
I don't sing unizo.
I'm good at pulling it out.
But I'm still pulling it out.
I'm looking around a lot.
I'm quick to notice when there's a problem.
Sometimes I think, "I'm impressed by your broad-mindedness.
I think he's calm.
Other than that...
When I'm like "Here and now, here and now, here and now, here and now.
She never misses.
Why are you so vocal?
How can you do that? You can get such a great energy from it.
I can really see the difference in the shrimp's energy between the presence and absence of Ms. Nakayama.
I can really see the difference in the energy of the prawns.
They are always working really hard.
I thought I sang with a crumpled up smile.
And Mr. Kobayashi and Mr. Shoji, as Team Ebituaries, I'd like to praise myself for the members of the team.
I think Kobayashi's name might come up a lot.
It's so cool and refreshing.
It's so cool and refreshing, and it's so cool and refreshing.
More than anyone else.
I felt it last summer at Lake Yamanaka.
I felt it last summer at the Fami performance at Lake Yamanaka.
It's pretty hard to do a Fami-Performance.
The audience goes wild with the songs
We play the hardest songs all the time without much break.
It's a summer tradition for Ebi Junior High School as well as the University Performance held at Saitama Super Arena in March.
It's a summer tradition in Ebichu
Running around the venue under the scorching sun
We performed 46 songs in 2 days!
In the midst of all that
Still singing in unison all the time
And it was the emotion of the last song
I know it's a Kobayashi song, but
but he sounded so stable.
Yes.
The two of them were proud of themselves as Team Ebichu. It was the last song of the live in the intense heat
Kaho Kobayashi's voice showed her 46th song.
Here it is!
May you be filled with wonderful memories
I can't listen to you because I love you, where the fleeting future is
When I touched your blooming skin
Now is the time when I cried
And yet, when you said you weren't sure
I'm so worried about you, aren't I?
I'll be fine.
No, really.
I worry the most.
He comes to me the most.
No matter what show I'm doing.
They come all over the venue.
They come to my dressing room.
I wonder if I'm going to be okay today.
I tell them I'm fine, but...
But I'm still a bit of a worrier.
Thank you for watching!
One of the attractions of Ebitu Live is the unique costumes that change from park to park.
Some are junior high school uniforms, others are bright and colorful for the summer outdoor concerts.
Sometimes chic and sophisticated, there are many variations!
So, Stackroll Search!
This time, we'd like to focus on this Ms. Satoyama among the costumes!
Hello!
This is Mr. Tact Satoyama, aka Takuti, a stylist.
Mr. Satoyama created the costumes for Ebichu.
Let's have a little fun with it.
In this costume, it looks like a diagonal border.
but there are letters written on it.
This is a summer costume
This is a summer costume.
It's made of a light and breathable material called "cardboard knit".
It is made of a light and breathable material called "cardboard knit", which is designed to survive outdoor live performances.
It takes about 2 weeks from the designing stage to the production stage.
When the costumes are almost finished, the members try them on and make final adjustments.
For example, in the case of a jacket style, if the front is tightened
It will be hard to lift up the garment.
In such cases, we add gussets under the armpits and so on.
or using a fabric with more stretch.
We make fine adjustments so that each member can perform at 100%.
We make fine adjustments so that each member can perform at their best.
Mayama is the type of person who makes her own movements according to the costume.
She's that type of person.
She doesn't make requests herself.
I think she thinks it's my job to wear what I'm given.
I think that's what she's trying to say.
Ms. Satoyama, the stylist, has an outfit that she would like to admire.
I happened to talk to these two in passing about the outfits.
So cute! That's from 2016.
Oh! I love that one so much!
Super cute!
Here's the outfit!
The first revolutionary yukata-like costume worn by Ebinaka!
The members call it "ero-sode" (erotic sleeves), but the sleeves were so revolutionary that even the fans thought it was a great idea to open up the sleeves and show the shoulders.
Finally, Ebinaka showed her shoulders.
I like the way Tacti shows her skin, it's very elegant.
Even with the shoulders showing, it looks really healthy.
I want to wear it.
Starscroll search for the artisans of Ebitu Live!
Next is a video of the production
Hello.
Good afternoon.
This is Mr. Shibamura, the producer of the production video.
I wonder what kind of video would contribute the most to the live performance.
I'm thinking about what kind of video would contribute the most to the live performance.
Mr. Shibamura's work covers a wide range of areas, such as filming and editing live performances, and creating cool videos for the opening and curtain-opening ceremonies.
Mr. Shibamura's work covers a wide range of areas, including filming and editing of live performances.
Some of them include VTRs like this one
How much does this T-shirt cost?
It's 3,700 yen including tax.
Is that cheap? Is it expensive?
Enmayuna's first-year students
Yes, a VTR that introduces internal goods in a nostalgic commercial style.
It would be boring to have the members come out and say what they recommend.
However, this is not a self-praise in itself.
but rather his persistence to entertain both newcomers and regulars.
Mr. Shibamura's persistence to entertain both newcomers and regulars is what he is praising himself for.
The video between the acts of the spring tour is changed for each show.
At the most, 14 videos were made!
So that fans who come again and again will not get bored!
The content is renewed for each show of the national tour.
In fact, we've made 14 VTRs!
My name is Cocona Sakuragi.
I use 100% EBISM penlights!
Some of them are solo like this one.
keychains.
When there are
I make the fans who have come to the concert feel excited by the local commercial-style VTR.
When I'm at a live concert, I take pictures of the audience on the monitor.
I take pictures on the monitor, but the audience is taking pictures
I wanted to see their reactions.
Stackroll search for "Ebituaries Live
The last one is direction.
Yusuke directing Ebitu's live performance
Hello.
We have decided on the concept of the live and the set list to suit it.
Lighting and monitors, etc.
The conductor in charge of everything.
The members of Ebitu are very particular about their live performance.
So we have to make sure that we can bring out the best of each member's talent.
We are trying to find the right balance to bring out the best of each member's talent.
Thank you for watching!
The concept of the 10th anniversary tour in 2022 is a museum.
The performance was linked to the paintings on the stage.
In addition, a member in a car appeared from the painting.
The performance was staged as if they were driving through the city at night.
The tension of the members as well as the fans was raised.
Thank you for watching!
Yusuke's self-praise is such a good thing.
It's a song called "As You Are" from the New Year's college arts and crafts show.
It's a rather fast-paced and positive song.
Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku is, in my mind, a kind of youth.
So when I wanted to express that youth somehow in this song
I told the members that I wanted them to run forward in the chorus part of the song.
Music
In order to add an expression of youth to the positivity of the song
I asked them to run as fast as they could, not just run.
Here is the scene
Ayaka Yasumoto sang the chorus as fast as she could.
It was quite difficult for Ayaka Yasumoto to sing the chorus because it was hard for her to catch the pitch of the song due to her breathing becoming unsteady.
I asked her to sing the chorus as fast as she could, but she said she would give it a try.
She said she would give it a try.
She sang as hard as she could while stamping her feet on the spot at every rehearsal.
She sang as hard as she could.
She sang with a straight and youthful style without any blurriness, and I was really impressed by her performance.
Yusuke's other self-praise is the direction he gave to this jump.
This song was the turning point when Ebitu was a six-member group.
It was created with the image of the girls struggling to break through the darkness.
I think it's a song with so much energy that it overwhelms you.
I think it also has a bit of a dark image.
It's a song that we always perform in such a way.
But this time, Saitama Super Arena is scheduled
I wanted to create a bright image of jumping high toward the goal.
I wanted to create a bright image.
I wanted to create a bright image, or to move forward toward a new goal.
We added 5 new members who had never existed before.
The members gave their opinions and reached the goal of jumping forward.
Nori and Alexa's top impression
I like the fact that you were trying to count 點 at a high level in the solution kalau
Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching.
I don't mean to just ask you to do it cheerfully.
I just want each of you to express yourselves in a way that makes people look forward.
I want you to be able to push people's backs up, to rise high.
I want you to sing the song "Jump" in such a way that you can push people's backs.
We discussed over and over whether or not we could sing the song "Jump.
After many discussions and arguments, we came up with a new form of "Jump" that we all created together.
I think we all came up with this new form of "Jump".
That's why it's here now.